# Diki Candra Setiawan

Wonogiri, Central Java, Indonesia



dikisetiawan81@gmail.com



081230047245



linkedin.com/in/dikicandrasetiawan



https://dhikicheeks.github.io

# Summary

A Programming Code Enthusiast since 2013, has the ability to develop websites and mobile apps, with various programming languages and frameworks such as laravel, codeigniter, bootstrap, ajax, javascript, php, sql database, c++, vb, flutter mobile, etc.

## **Experience**



# 😚 Mobile Application Developer

PT Regarsport Industri Indonesia Feb 2022 - Present (6 months +)



## Web Programmer

PT Regarsport Industri Indonesia Apr 2021 - Present (1 year 4 months +)

# Production Operator

PT. Altinex Aug 2018 - Feb 2020 (1 year 7 months)

## **Education**



### SMK Negeri 1 Bulukerto

Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak 2015 - 2018



## SMP Negeri 2 Slogohimo

2012 - 2015



### SD Negeri 2 Sokoboyo

2006 - 2012

#### Skills

Dart • Pengembangan Android • Laravel • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Codelgniter • AJAX • Bootstrap • Flutter • MySQL